

#### Personal Info

**4** +40 768 708 522

<u>alexandru.nedelcu.office@gmail.com</u>

Bucharest, Romania

#### Links

- ➤ Linkedin
- ➤ <u>GitHub</u>
- > Portfolio

## Skills

- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Python & Tkinter
- Git & Control Version
- WordPress & Elementor
- Interpersonal skills
- Collaboration skills
- Chrome DevTools
- Jira System
- Office & Google Workspace
- Adobe Photoshop
- Graphic Design
- Team management

## Languages

- English
- Русский
- Romanian

Proactive and passionate **software developer** with experience in creating, improving, and completing web applications and projects, with a background in **web design**, E-commerce, custom brand graphics, and marketing. Focused on streamlining, optimizing, and managing processes. I look for opportunities to grow, connect to people, and develop my skills. Also interested in automation and data analysis. I am always learning and having fun doing it.

## Work Experience

# Technical Support Specialist (remote), Valoris

July 2023

- Technical support for software issues and troubleshooting problems in the Kyocera Document Solutions project.
- Working with clients from the Porsche Group Romania (porsche, audi, skoda, lamborghini, wv, bentley etc.)

#### QA Game Tester, Greenlink

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

- Collaborated on a small project with a team of testers to identify, isolate and report bugs. Using Jira to accurately document, track and report issues found during testing.
- Created detailed reports and personally collaborated directly with developers to identify potential areas of improvement.

# Customer Relations Agent, IQBox

2021 - 2022

- Generated ~44%+ more sales than the average employee every month, through optimising work and a more effective approach.
- Trained a team of 5 people with ~38% more sales than the average.
- Specialist in the representative company's team meetings regarding the big change of the company's Telecom partner to Vodafone in 2021.
- Personally implemented more effective low-end target strategies in the department.
- Proficient in data entry, CRM systems and document management.

## Web Designer Freelancer

2020 - 2021

- Designed and developed E-commerce websites and landing pages with Wordpress and Elementor.
- Integrated Facebook Pixel Analytics for sales and leads tracking.
- Maintained and administered websites, including updating contents and improving user experience.
- Experience in troubleshooting and debugging issues related to website design, user data, gdpr, chat, payment and translation.

# **Education and Courses**

- Complete Web Developer, Studioweb
- Python Basic, Step IT
- Business Finance and Entrepreneurship, Dalles GO

• The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp, Udemy

# Backup links:

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandru-nedelcu-office/
- ➤ <a href="https://github.com/UmbraNova">https://github.com/UmbraNova</a>
- https://umbranova.github.io/My-Portfolio-Project/